<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Creating a new Proof Project">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This cheat sheet shows you how to create a new Proof Project to hold your proof scripts, then add some scripts.
<br/><br/>
Your new Proof Project will hold all your proof scripts for processing together.
Files must be added to a project before they can be used in Proof General.
      </description>
   </intro>
	
	<item title="Launch the Proof Project Wizard">
		<!--  pluginId was org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets -->
		<!--  action
			pluginId="ed.inf.proofgeneral"
			class="ed.inf.proofgeneral.wizards.NewProofProjectWizard.CheatSheetAction" -->
		<!-- command serialization="ed.inf.proofgeneral.wizards.NewProofProjectWizard.newProject()"/ -->
      <description>
         On the File menu, select <b>New &gt; Project...</b>.
		<br/><br/>
		From the selection of available wizards, expand the Proof General folder, and select <b>Proof Project</b>.
		<br/><br/>
		Confirm your selection by pressing <b>Next</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Name your project" dialog="false" skip="false">
      <description>
         The next page of the wizard will appear.  <b>Name</b> your project as you 
		 wish (though remember this must also be a valid direcrory name).
		 <br/><br/>
		In general it is sensible to <b>use default location</b>, but be aware this
		might not be your preferred &apos;documents&apos; store if you downloaded Proof General 
		 to a temporary location.
		 <br/><br/>
		Press <b>Finish</b> to create your project.  You will find your newly created
		project in the <b>Project Explorer</b> view, and can now add files to your
		project.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create a new script" dialog="false" skip="true">
      <description>
         This allows you to create a new script from a template.  You can skip this step if you want to import a file.
		<br/><br/>
		From the <b>File</b> menu, select <b>New &gt; Proof Script</b>.
		<br/><br/>
		Enter the Theory&apos;s <b>name</b> into the first box (The file name will be automatically generated).  If 
		<b>container</b> is blank, click <b>Browse</b> to select your new project; otherwise you can accept the default.
		<br/><br/>
		Press <b>Finish</b> to create your template file.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Import an existing script" dialog="false" skip="true">
      <description>
         You must <b>import</b> existing theory files on disk in order to use them in scripting.
		<br/><br/>
		From the <b>File</b> menu, select <b>Import...</b>
		<br/><br/>
		From the wizard, select <b>General &gt; File System</b>; press <b>Next</b>.
		<br/><br/>
		Type the directory containing your file into <b>from</b>, or find it using <b>browse</b>.  Beneath here, directories 
		appear on the left; files on the right.  &apos;Tick&apos; files you wish to import.  Accept the default import location 
		(or browse to find another project or project sub-folder).
		<br/><br/>
		Press <b>Finish</b> to import your selected files.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="View your proof script" dialog="false" skip="false">
      <description>
         Your proof script should now appear in the <b>Proof Explorer</b> view,
		to the left of your screen by default.  You can view any one of these
		scripts by double-clicking on its entry.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
